saleen.com 2019-07-24

# PRIVACY POLICY | Saleen

We respect and are committed to protecting your privacy.  That is why we have adopted this Privacy Policy.  This Privacy Policy lets you know how and for what purposes we are collecting, processing and using your Personal Information (as defined herein).  We pledge that we will take reasonable steps to ensure that your Personal Information will only be used in ways that are in compliance with this Privacy Policy.

This Privacy Policy is in effect for any web pages, mobile applications, third party social media sites, e-mail lists, non user-specific information and personal information collected and/or owned by Saleen Automotive, Inc (“Saleen”, “our” or “we”), including but not limited to the Saleen website(s), no matter the method of collection (e.g., mail, facsimile, sign-up/sign-in page, survey), including collection through this website and any online features, services and/or programs offered by Saleen (collectively, the “Website”).

Notwithstanding the foregoing, this Privacy Policy is not applicable to any other web pages, mobile applications, social media sites, e-mail lists, generic information and Personal Information collected and/or owned by any entity other than Saleen, including, but not limited to, any automobile dealership or service center.  Users of the foregoing resources should refer to the Privacy Policy in effect for the applicable owner.

Your use of the Website is also governed by our Terms and Conditions.

This Privacy Policy does not apply to information collected by Saleen through a means other than the Web Site.  If the same information is collected through the Web Site and through a means other than the Web Site, the terms of this Privacy Policy shall apply.

**Your California Privacy Rights**

Under California’s “Shine the Light” law, California residents who provide personal information in connection with obtaining products or services for personal, family or household use are entitled to request and obtain from us once a calendar year information about the customer information we shared, if any, with other businesses for their own direct marketing uses.  If applicable, this information would include the categories of customer information and the names and addresses of those businesses with which we shared customer information for the immediately prior calendar year (e.g., requests made in 2015 will receive information regarding 2014 sharing activities).

To obtain this information on behalf of Saleen, please send an email message to privacy@saleen.com with “Request for California Privacy Information” in the subject line and in the body of your message.  We will provide the requested information to you at your e-mail address in response.

Please be aware that not all information sharing is covered by the “Shine the Light” requirements and only information on covered sharing will be included in our response.

Additionally, because we may collect your Personal Information from time to time, California’s Online Privacy Protection Act requires us to disclose how we respond to “do not track” requests and other similar mechanisms. Currently, our policy is that we do not recognize “do not track” requests from Internet browsers and similar devices.

**How Information Is Collected**

The types of Personal Information we collect may include, among other things (collectively, “Personal Information”): (1) contact information (e.g., name, address, home and mobile telephone numbers, email address); (2) biographical information such as household data, preferences, and demographic information (e.g., date of birth, gender, marital status); (3) Internet protocol (or IP) address or device ID/UDID; (4) mother’s maiden name (parent’s name prior to marriage); (5) drivers’ license numbers; (6) asset and income information; (7) bank account and credit/debit card numbers; (8) racial or ethnic origin; (9) purchase information regarding our products and services; and (10) vehicle identification numbers (VIN’s).

The means by which Saleen collects such personal information may include when you: (1) purchase, order, or request information about our products and services through the Web Site; (2) access a Saleen social media platform; (3) sign up for e-mail notifications, electronic newsletters, mobile messages (including SMS), or social media notifications from, or on behalf of, Saleen; (4) enter or participate in a Saleen contest, event, promotion or sweepstakes, or respond to one of our surveys; (5) provide Saleen with comments, suggestions or other input through the Web Site; and (6) create a user account for use in connection with the Website (your “User Account”).  Saleen also collects such personal information in our marketing efforts on third party websites.

We may also receive information about you from third party sources, using Personal Information collected through the Website as the method of identifying you.  Our use of that third party-sourced information will be subject to this Privacy Policy.

Saleen or a partner may sponsor promotions, sweepstakes or contests through the Website.  Your participation is entirely voluntary.  Users may be asked to provide personally identifiable information including, but not limited to, your name, email address or home address or to answer questions in order to participate.  Saleen may also transfer Personal Information to certain advertising or marketing partners from whom you have requested to receive information.

**Additional Ways that Information is Collected Through the Website**

    Browser Log Files: Our servers automatically log each visitor to the Website and collect and record certain information about each visitor.  This information includes or may include your “Internet Protocol”, or IP, address, browser language, browser type, operating system, domain names, browsing history (including time spent at a domain, time and date of your visit), referring/exit web pages and URLs, and number of clicks.  The domain name and IP address reveal nothing personal about the visitor other than the IP address from which the user has accessed the Website.

    Cookies: From time to time, Saleen and/or our advertisers or other third parties may send a “cookie” to your computer.  A cookie is a small piece of data that is sent to your Internet browser from a web server and stored on your computer’s hard drive and that can be re-sent to the serving website on subsequent visits.  A cookie, by itself, cannot read other data from your hard disk or read other cookie files already on your computer.  A cookie, by itself, does not damage your system.  We, our advertisers and other third parties may use cookies to identify and keep track of, among other things, those areas of the Website and third party websites that you have visited in the past in order to enhance your next visit to the Website.  You can choose whether or not to accept cookies by changing the settings of your Internet browser, but some functionality of the Website may be impaired or not function as intended if you choose not to accept cookies.  See the Third Party Opt Out section below.

    Web Beacons: Some of our web pages and electronic communications may contain images, which may or may not be visible to you, known as Web Beacons (sometimes referred to as “clear gifs”).  Web Beacons collect only limited information that includes a cookie number; time and date of a page view; and a description of the page on which the Web Beacon resides.  We may also carry Web Beacons placed by third party advertisers.  These Web Beacons do not carry any Personal Information and are only used to track usage of the Website and activities associated with the Website. See the Third Party Opt Out section below.

    Unique Identifier:  We may assign you a unique internal identifier to help keep track of your future visits. We use this information to gather aggregate demographic information about our visitors, and we use it to personalize the information you see on the Website and some of the electronic communications you receive from us.  We keep this information for our internal use, and this information is not shared with others.

    Third Party Opt Out:  We may allow third-party companies to serve advertisements and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit the Website.  These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (including, but not limited to, click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to the Website in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you.  These companies typically use a cookie or third party Web Beacon to collect this information, as further described above.  Through these technologies, the third party may have access to and use non-personalized information about your online usage activity.

    You can opt-out of certain online behavioral services through any one of the ways described below (you do not need to go to each opt-out site, one is sufficient).  After you opt-out, you will continue to receive advertisements, but those advertisements will no longer be as relevant to you.

    •    You can configure your web browser (Chrome, Firefox, Internet Explorer, Safari, etc.) to delete and/or control the use of cookies. More information can be found in the Help system of your browser. It is at your discretion whether you use the opt-out described above or manage cookies via the browser.

Note: If you opt-out as described above, you should not delete your cookies.  If you delete your cookies, you will need to opt-out again.

**Use of Personal Information**

The Personal Information that we collect is used for four main purposes:

    1.    to enable the features of the Website, including, but not limited to: (a) operating any competitions or promotions in which you may participate; (b) setting up and managing your online account, including but not limited to our processing your requests for information, and/or providing support services to you; (c) providing services to you, such as providing you information about our vehicles;

    2.    to improve the Website by determining which of our products, features and services are most popular.  We may analyze your information and usage information to enable us and our affiliates to provide services to you and develop new features, functionality and services;

    3.    to personalize your experience on the Website; and

    4.    to communicate with you and to inform you about our and third parties’ products and services.  When requested by you, we (and/or any of our third party service providers) may send you and keep you updated with information about existing and new services, products and special offers, by email, telephone (including, but not limited to, SMS), mail or by means of any other contact details you provide to us or our affiliates, or to such third party service providers.

**When Information Is Disclosed By Saleen**

In addition to the other times or occasions on which we might disclose Personal Information about you, we might also disclose Personal Information when required by law or in the good-faith belief that such disclosure is necessary to: (1) comply with legal processes and applicable laws; (2) enforce this Privacy Policy; (3) respond to claims that any materials, documents, images, graphics, logos, designs, audio, video and any other information provided to, from or on the Website by you violates the rights of third parties; or (4) protect our rights, property or safety or the rights, property or personal safety of our visitors and the public.

We use reasonable precautions to keep the information that is disclosed to us secure.  We provide Personal Information and non-personally-identifiable information to our parent, subsidiary, affiliated companies, and other businesses or persons for the purposes of processing such information on our behalf and promoting the goods and services of our trusted business partners (for example, navigation system map updates), some or all of which may store your some or all information on servers outside of the United States.  We require that these parties agree to process such information in compliance with our Privacy Policy or in a similar, industry-standard manner, and we use reasonable efforts to limit their use of such information and to use other appropriate confidentiality and security measures.  The use of your information by one of our trusted business partners may be subject to that party’s own Privacy Policy.

We may share non-personally identifiable information (such as anonymous user usage data, referring/exit pages and URLs, platform types, number of clicks, etc.) with third parties to demonstrate the usage patterns for Saleen’s advertisements, content, functionality promotions and/or services on the Website and/or on third party websites.

We also reserve the right to disclose Personal Information and/or non-personally-identifiable information in connection with the enforcement of our Terms and Conditions referenced above, to take precautions against liability, to investigate and defend against any third-party claims or allegations, to assist government enforcement agencies, to protect the security or integrity of the Website, and to protect our rights, property, or personal safety of Saleen, and that of our users or others.

We reserve the right to transfer your Personal Information, as well as any other information, in connection with the sale or other disposition of all or part of the Saleen business and/or assets.  We also cannot make any representations regarding the use or transfer of your Personal Information or other information that we may have in the event of our bankruptcy, reorganization, insolvency, receivership or an assignment for the benefit of creditors, and you expressly agree and consent to the use and/or transfer of your Personal Information or other information in connection with a sale or transfer of some or all of our assets in any of the above described proceedings.  Furthermore, we cannot and will not be responsible for any breach of security by any third parties or for any actions of any third parties that receive any of the information that is disclosed to us.  The Website also links to a wide variety of other websites and the Website may contain advertisements of third parties.  We are not and cannot be responsible for the privacy policies of those websites of third parties or how they treat information (including, but not limited to personally identifiable information) about their users.

**User Account, Password, and Security**

For certain features available through the Website, we may require the use of encryption technologies provided for your protection and/or User Account.  We use reasonable precautions to protect the privacy of your UserID, password and User Account information.  You, however, are ultimately responsible for protecting your UserID, password and User Account information from disclosure to third parties, and you are not permitted to circumvent the use of required encryption technologies.  You agree to: (a) immediately notify Saleen of any unauthorized use of your UserID, password and/or User Account, and/or any other breach of security; and (b) ensure that you log out from your User Account at the end of each session.  While we may provide certain encryption technologies and use other reasonable precautions to protect your confidential information and provide suitable security, we do not and cannot guarantee or warrant that information transmitted through the internet is secure, or that such transmissions are free from delay, interruption, interception or error.

**Employment Opportunity Information Collection**

For individuals interested in job opportunities with Saleen, the Website links prospective employees to a partner’s website.  The partner’s website, which has its own Privacy Policy, collects Personal Information from prospective employees for human resources recruitment purposes.  This information is then shared with Saleen’s human resources department and others within Saleen who are involved in the recruitment process.  The foregoing also applies to job application inquiries that you may transmit to us other than through the Website.

**Information From Children**

We do not collect Personal Information from any person that we know to be under the age of thirteen (13).  Specifically, the Website is not intended or designed to attract children under the age of thirteen (13).  You affirm that you are either more than 18 years of age, or an emancipated minor, or possess legal parental or guardian consent, and are fully able and competent to enter into the terms, conditions, obligations, affirmations, representations, and warranties set forth in this Privacy Policy, and to abide by and comply with this Privacy Policy. In any case, you affirm that you are over the age of 13, as THE WEBSITE IS NOT INTENDED FOR CHILDREN UNDER 13 THAT ARE UNACCOMPANIED BY HIS OR HER PARENT OR LEGAL GUARDIAN.

Parents should be aware that Saleen’s Privacy Policy will govern our use of Personal Information, but also that information that is voluntarily given by children – or others – in e-mail exchanges, bulletin boards or the like may be used by other parties to generate unsolicited communications.  Saleen encourages all parents to instruct their children in the safe and responsible use of their Personal Information while using the Internet.

**Privacy Outside the Website**

The Website may contain various links to other websites, including, but not limited to, links to websites of various third party service providers.  Saleen is not and cannot be responsible for the privacy practices or the content of any of those other websites.  Other than under agreements with certain reputable organizations and companies, and except for third party service providers (as described in this Privacy Policy), we do not share any of the Personal Information that you provide to us with any of the websites to which the Website links, although we may share aggregate, non-personally identifiable information with those other third parties.  Please check with those websites in order to determine their privacy policies and your rights under them.

**European Union Users**

If you are visiting us from the European Union, please note that we may transfer your Personal Information outside the European Union for use for any of the purposes described in this Privacy Policy.  By using the Website and providing us with your Personal Information, you consent to such transfer of your Personal Information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

**Choices With Your Personal Information**

Whether you submit any Personal Information to Saleen is entirely up to you.  You are under no obligation to provide Personal Information. However, this information is essential for the provision and quality of some of the services we offer to you, so we cannot provide you with certain services if you choose to withhold requested information.

You may choose to prevent Saleen from disclosing or using your Personal Information under certain circumstances (“opt out”).  You may opt out of any disclosure or use of your Personal Information for purposes that are incompatible with the purpose(s) for which it was originally collected or for which you subsequently gave authorization by notifying us by one of the methods at the end of this Privacy Policy, or by following the procedures set forth in an electronic communication from us, if applicable.  Furthermore, even where your Personal Information is to be disclosed and used in accordance with the stated purposes in this Privacy Policy, you may elect to opt out of such disclosure to and use by a third party that is not acting as an agent of Saleen.  There are some uses from which you cannot opt-out, such as our use of your Personal Information in connection with your ownership status of a vehicle or vehicle recall (and similar) notification procedures.

Please note that opting out of the disclosure and use of your Personal Information as a prospective employee may prevent you from being hired as an employee by Saleen to the extent you are using this Website to apply for an open position.

If Saleen collects Personal Information from you, such information will not be disclosed or used by Saleen for purposes that are incompatible with the purpose(s) for which it was originally collected or for which you subsequently gave authorization unless you affirmatively consent to such disclosure and use.

You may opt out of online behavioral advertising by following the instructions set forth above under the above section “Additional Ways That Information Is Collected Through the Website,” subsection “Third Party Opt Out.”

**Access and Correction**

To access your Personal Information in the possession of Saleen and correct inaccuracies of that information in our records, please contact us in the manner specified at the end of this Privacy Policy.  We ask individuals to identify themselves and the information requested to be accessed and amended before processing such requests, and we may decline to process requests in limited circumstances as permitted by applicable privacy legislation.

**Your Consent To This Privacy Policy**

By using the Website, you consent to the collection and use of you information (including Personal Information) by us as specified above or as we otherwise see fit, in compliance with this Privacy Policy, unless you inform us otherwise by means of the procedure identified below.  If we decide to change this Privacy Policy, we will make an effort to post those changes on this web page so that you will always be able to understand what information we collect, how we use that information and under what circumstances we may disclose that information to others.  Your use of the Website following your acceptance of any amendment of this Privacy Policy will signify your assent to and acceptance of its revised terms for all previously collected information and information collected from you in the future.  We may use comments, information or feedback that you may submit in any manner that we may choose without notice or compensation to you.

_Copyright © 2016. Saleen Automotive, Inc.   All Rights Reserved._
